恭喜！ 你已经完成了这个程序的整体轮廓
Hurray, you're done implementing wire frames for the app! Now
现在我们开始对应用的细节进行雕琢，应用一些风格和Views
comes the visual polish part, where we tweak the styles
让app看着炫起来。
and the views to make the app look awesome. Here
这些是一些程序效果图，当我们的app完成后就是介个样子滴
are the visual mocks, for what the app should look
如果你的团队里有设计师
like, when we're done. If you work with a designer,
那么他们还会给在其中你画出一些红色标记。
they should also give you red lines. Red lines specify
这些标记包括尺寸、字体风格、颜色、空白区域等等
everything from sizes, font styles, colors, spacing, et cetera. This
通过这些参数可以帮助你构造较为完美的布局以贴近效果图
should help you achieve pixel perfect layouts that match the
那么我们如何处理这些数据呢？
visual mocks. How did we come up with these values?
这里我们用到了Android设计指南，指南里有和度量与网格相关的信息
Well we used the Android design guide, which has information on
我们使用这些信息来满足程序设计的需要
metrics and grids, and we adapted them to fit our
你可以点击这个链接获得更多内容。
app's needs. You can click on the link for more info.